export const QuestionData = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following HTML tag is used to create an unordered list?",
    options: ["<ol></ol>", " <ul></ul>", "<li></li>", "<ll></ll>"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is the use of id() function in python?",
    options: [
      "Id returns the identity of the object",
      "Every object doesnâ€™t have a unique id",
      "All of the mentioned",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which datatype can store unstructured data in a column?",
    options: [" CHAR", "RAW", "NUMERIC", " VARCHAR"],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the toLocateString() method do in JS?",
    options: [
      "Returns a localised object representation",
      "Returns a localised string representation of an object",
      "Returns parsed string",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following property controls the horizontal overflow of a block or inline block?",
    options: ["overflow-x", "overflow", "overflow-y", "overflow-k"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What does A.I. stand for?",
    options: [
      "Anti intellectual",
      "Automatic intelligent",
      "Artificial intelligence",
      "Non of these",
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following statements is correct about the formal parameters in C++?",
    options: [
      "Parameters with which functions are called",
      "Parameters which are used in the definition of the function",
      "Variables other than passed parameters in a function",
      "Variables that are never used in the function",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What helps react for keeping their data unidirectional?",
    options: ["jsx", "props", "flux", "Dom"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which data structure is needed to convert infix notation to postfix notation?",
    options: ["Tree", "Branch", "Stack", "Queue"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "How many layers are there in the ISO OSI reference model?",
    options: ["7", "5", "4", "6"],
    answer: 1,
  },
];
